Hello,
hello friends, welcome to Extra Officer,
friends, HDFC Bank report for our readers has
arrived. Before the results are released, I
would like to tell you one thing. HDFC Bank will
give a different this time, but there is nothing mentioned about China in this notice.
Actually, after this notice, the
company has filed another notice, in which there is a mention of
different. So, let's
read the results once.
After that, that
notice will also be seen at the end of the video and it will be understood what is
written about that medicine. First, you should see one thing here, only then
you will see the numbers here in the leg. So, let's
start here first with the total income. Let me
adjust it a little. Yes, okay, the
total income is written here. This is the
number for this quarter, and this is the number for the previous quarter, that is, for
quarter three, and this is the
number for the quarter last year. I will
zoom in on it once so that you can
understand it better. Last year, the
quarter format of HDFC Bank's total income was 38 lakhs,
which has
increased to 41 lakhs in this quarter.  8 thousand 578
in the previous quarter, that is, in water three it was 40
lakh 65 thousand 160, so you can say that this
revenue is getting a good rise
and water number is also quite good when
seen here, then you
can say that the income has been very good
but it will not be enough just by looking at the income, it is
very important for us to keep an eye on the expenses of the company as well
because we can see the effect of expenses
in the profit figures of the company,
total expense is
written here but there is no promise add in it yet,
this time the only expense of HDFC Bank has been
24 lakh 72 thousand 870 which
was 22 lakh 48 thousand 469 in the quarter form last year
and in the previous quarter it
was 23 lakh 87 thousand 265, here the
expenses have increased year after year and quarter after quarter
also an increase in expenses is being seen, but there is no
denying it, but if the expenses increase then the
expenses also increase but more  The
problem arises only when the expenses increase. Look here, the
operating profit of the company is written
before adding 24%, before adding tax etc., it is
written here as 100 lakh 35 thousand
701. This time the total profit of HDFC Bank
is there but now there will be process -
then there will be tax as well, after that you will
get to see the main profit, last year it was 15
lakh 53 thousand 270 which has increased to
35 thousand 701 this time and
in the previous quarter i.e. in quarter three it was
16 lakh 77 thousand
595, so we are seeing the effect of the expense here,
hence the profit has decreased a bit
in this quarter as compared to the previous quarter,
but this
year's profit has come out to be higher as compared to last year
and this is important friends, now
look here, after providing for this amount, the
profit left in the hands of the company
is 100 lakh
4466. Now after doing the text in it, the text will be there,
this time the profit in the hands of the company  The
main profit that is left, which is the net profit, is Rs
10 lakh 5 thousand 518. HDFC Bank's
net profit last year was Rs 800000 18,000
651 and in the previous quarter it was Rs 10 lakh
34 thousand 220. Compared to last year, this year there is a
good increase in profit,
but compared to the previous quarter, the
profit is a little less, but there is no
problem with this. Nothing happens to such a
big company, such a good
company, just because 12 quarters have passed. This last P
is our earnings of Rs 10 lakh 5518. Look, the
company has lost a little in that, so there is no need to worry, there is no
need to panic.
If it is in your portfolio, then you
can easily fold it. Let's take a look at the
Ps here. Last year, the fourth
point here was 9 and this time it
was 18 points in water three and this time it has become 18
points. Now, it is natural that the profit has
decreased, so this too will decrease a little.  Let's
see the NPA of the company here, it is
quite an imported recipe, here
first the gross NPA is written, this time the
gross NPA is 16 lakh 14 thousand 966, which
was 16 lakh 1355 in the previous quarter
and
15 lakh 8 thousand 602 in the previous year's quarter form, I would like to say one thing here
that whatever numbers you see in the country, all of them are
very important,
I should not get caught up in one thing except this
and hello friends, along with this, there is
also a thing called providence and promise,
in the results, I mean,
you will see all this in the results of all the stocks of the banking sector, so it is
very important to understand NPA and providence,
these mean non-performing assets,
what do they mean, what is the liquidity of the bank,
it is money, it
means that a loan has been given to someone and it is
not being recovered from there, such money which is stuck,
this is called inc, then the
power that is there, then search for it, the bank itself is thinking
that the money is lost.  It is
categorized by profession. Therefore,
remember that in the balance sheets of the banking sector and finance
companies, whatever stocks there are, these
provident funds
and investment instruments should always be included. This
proves to be good for these companies.
Here, in the case of HDFC, you
can see that there is a slight increase in gross NPAs compared to last year,
and the gross NPAs have also increased slightly in this quarter from the previous quarter.
However,
one thing to keep in mind here is that
this is HDFC Bank. Its reputation is a
little big, but this will
not destroy any company. It decreases
when their losses keep increasing like this
and there is no trace of profit.
Therefore, it becomes very important to check the companies' quarterly results every time.
This is where the truth is revealed. The
net NPA is also written below here. You
can see it if you want, and it is
also given here as a percentage. To
understand in short, you
can also see it here.  After the process, let's take
a look at it and compare it with the
nearest quarter.
Look here, the providence is written.
This time the providence is
331,233. This is less than last year. Last year it was
469,370
and in the previous quarter, it was
299,398. As per the above, the process has decreased, which is a
good thing, but the water and quarter has
increased a little. According to
me, the
quarterly result of HDFC Bank was good. This
can happen for 12 quarters in the short term. This does
not ruin any company. But every time the
number came, every Balaghat
number came, if the profession ampere is filled then there is a
problem, but this will
not happen in the case of HDFC. Now let's
investigate a little about the difference medicine.
As I said, HDFC Bank will give a
difference, but in the result notice, there was nothing
written about deletion.
After presenting the results, another
notice was filed by the companies. Look here, it is
written about life on 23rd April.
A board meeting has been fixed by the board of directors of the company, in
which the issue will be considered, then if the issue is
approved then its shareholders will
get the issue, so friends,
if you liked the information then
please like this video and if you are
new to this channel then keep subscribing to this channel
because
we keep bringing updates related to the share market on this channel, so that's all for
now, we will meet
in the next video, till then goodbye.